Filming inside the theater
Recording is a crime.
By law, those with less than 10 years of listening experience
role, or 10 million yen
Withdrawal of the following, or
Both
You can earn money.
If you see suspicious behavior
Then, go to the theater.
Please advise.
Gnome
The movie Dorobon.
This movie was shot in less than a day.
Then comes Musha.
Take me and
Take San's head.
Why do you think so?
Can it be done?
I bit it, just
There is no logic to this.
The other kids, I
Use yourself to get it
I understand that
I don't think so.
I can only rely on you
An unstoppable order.
That man lost his head.
It won't die even if you cut it.
Probably destroys Muzan.
It is not just the light of the fire that
I don't think so.
Even if you break my neck,
If he doesn't die, the fire
The wage war until the
It will be.
Good, that's good.
If it's a favor.
thank you.
Please, this already
That's it, my precious child.
We won't die
I hope so.
Follow me now
Are you planning to pack it?
You guys are going now
It's hell.
You filthy devils,
Tonight everyone is urushi
Let's do it.
Going to hell
That's a waste of your time.
I will never let you get away. Let's try it.
What can be done
Then, Scythe Battle Giro.
Defeat it!
It's a transfer business!
What is this place?
Up and down, left and right, up and down.
Take the enemy's end.
Is it Patnaru?
The situation before and after
Don't you understand?
Tamayosan cuts down on waste
It was crowded.
But how long will it last?
I don't know.
Calm down, Master Kanro.
yes!
Don't leave.
Huff huff huff
Haha are you okay?
Ha thank you
Ha, that helps
Water breathing passage
look over
I'll carry it haha haha
Huff huff huff
Ha ha ha ha
Ah, water breathing
The third person
Mejunzeyu
Ryumai haa
Ha ha ha ha munch
is amazing
What will happen with my slight movement?
Is that a technique?
Haak and then I
They showed their skills and
Not compatible
Moves like
This guy is crazy
This is the face of my feelings
Uuuuuuuuh
This is probably the Shinazu River.
Iglo said.
It must be the demon's foot.
Then, we
The strange things collected here
The purpose is to include the pillars
One layer of the mysterious murder
Please pay more attention.
Yes, yes.
Let's go!
Elio Koshu That person
The eternal sky
In Cambodia
Get closer, garbage
Haa, Iguro is saved.
There are no injuries.
Garbage is shit
Iguro's Cosmos
Don't let him have the power of Kagenpeibo
Will this be enough for me?
We are also exhausted
I intend to make
The parent
People were excited about the past
The majestic Sayotata
That person is found by the demon
Such a failure
I don't think so.
Take yourself
Yes.
Four years have passed
Because there was no
Dear Parent,
The boss said that I was attacked by a demon.
The boundaries of the mind are broken
When I was wandering
Please continue to encourage me.
The Ambassador of the time
Ours too
I was doing that
Like a Father
Ah, I know the unofficial
Not just my brother
They even took our father away.
No participation, no participation, beaten to death
Show me the hell I'll do it to you
Let's do it, rest assured, everyone is the same
I think, parents
I couldn't protect
One after the other, the movements
Bring it on
I'll kill you all.
once again
Just one more time
Once more, once more
Once again, what
Here's my screw or something else
Everyone is like a big brother
Please keep it up
I heard a sound
Is he nearby?
I might not forgive
That guy
I will never forgive you
Here is something something something something something something something something something something something something
Something something something something something something something something something something something something something something something
Later, to Nakime-chan
Thank you
I have to say it
Shinomu's Murdered Body
Stop it
You are stubborn.
Although it is stretched
Really stubborn
Maybe Shinom
The happiness of an ordinary girl
Get it, grandma
Until
I want you to live
Enough is enough
I will never quit
Something
Be sure to tell me
What kind of demon is it and when?
I can't pay for what I did to you
Tell me something like this
I'm just like normal.
I can't live
From the head
Covered in blood
It was such a demon.
No, no, nice to meet you
My name is
Doma, what a nice night
With a smile
Laugh heartily
Calmly and kindly
Speak well
Help me help me
Shi
You're talking now, right?
OK?
Wow!
That's fast. Is it a pillar?
a!
It's okay, just leave it there
I'll catch up with you later.
Because I'll eat properly
When that demon uses
A sharp dialect
I am the leader of the All Saints Paradise Sect
With everyone at Nano Shrine
It's my job to be happy
Not a single child was left behind
I'll eat cleanly
This guy
The demon who killed my sister
Everyone's happiness was released
This person dislikes
Please help me
Because I was looking for it
I would have saved you.
The child is already suffering
It's not spicy either.
No one to be afraid of
Everyone dies.
Because I'm scared
I'm the one feeding them.
Living with
Let's go on forever
I want to know the thoughts of the shrines.
Blood and flesh firmly
Accept and save,
The courage that leads to
I don't think so.
Is your head okay?
I really hate it
Uuuu, even though it's our first meeting
It's quite soluble.
Hey, I see.
Poor thing, something's wrong
I heard that something happened.
Let me help you.
Look, there's nothing spicy.
Someone killed my sister
You are the one who owns this haori.
Do you recognize
Ah, using the flower breath
The girl was so kind.
She was a cute girl.
The morning sun rises and I eat there
I remember you were a sleepy kid.
Eat properly
How about giving it to me?
My breathing stops a lot
Still can't see it. Amazing.
Pull it out with your hands
I couldn't stop it
Research
Pulsar high-con stand out
Hi-Lo Taclaw
It stands out
Wow it's so fast
But it's inconvenient, the gap
Standing with your stomach together
It's a no-brainer after all.
I'll cut my neck if I don't
Les can't be killed
How about me?
Bone poison works on the upper limit
Now I know if
Please, sister!
This is Louis's. It's you, it's you, it's you.
The poison used on Louis' mountain
It's more powerful after all.
The information was shared
Poison is a powerful source of information
If you change it to each demon,
I lost that one too
Uuuuuuuu
Oh, it can break down poison.
It seems like that happened.
Sorry
Even though you used it,
When you put it away
The sound is unique. I wonder if they are changing the poison information there.
Wowwwwwwwwwwwwwwww
Eat the fun poison
It's funny
The next information
Then I think you should listen.
Let's see it now.
That's fine. I hope you enjoy it.
Up until this area
Because I don't expect it.
Is the compounding done?
Come anytime
It's okay
I said try it.
But it's boring to use the same technique.
Not the same technique
That would be boring.
Huh?
From earlier
It's slow
This is not our
Please breathe now
It happened!
Huh?
Did you give me a little?
Resistance is well received
It was washed away. Amazing.
I was interested in the tears
It is the culmination of hard work.
Feel free to come, poison
Before decomposition,
I'm adamant that you should point out the attack.
I want to support the people who are posting
That's what happens.
This is already good
I've been a good boy since I was a child.
He was wise and smart.
When will these poor people be killed?
Because I helped you.
That made me happy
Because it is my mission
A rainbow in this child's eyes
The hair of the white crane
Hair is proof of innocence
is a special child, I'm sure God
I can hear the voice
My parents' stupidity
It seemed hopeless.
Otherwise, paradise religion etc.
A boring religion
I can't make it
Because I felt sorry for him.
Always talk
I gave it to you
I have never heard the voice of God
At first, I couldn't surpass it.
They all gathered together in worship
As expected,
I'm in trouble
Crying to the child
It's painful, what should I do?
Adults who say it's okay
Is your head okay?
I'm worried
Fiery
After telling my story
Please lead me to paradise
I want it
was lowered
I cried
Poor paradise
It doesn't exist, humans
I imagined and created
It's a time story.
There is no God or Buddha
Such a simple thing
These people have been
I'm alive
It's not because
When you die, you become nothing
I just can't feel anything
My heart stopped and my brain
Stop and rot
Just return to earth
As a living thing, everything
So it looks bitter
Such a simple thing
I can't accept it
It's hard to be stupid
Make the poor people happy
I want to
I want to help
For that reason, I
I was born
The fifth time, this also doesn't work.
Please listen to it
It's getting harder
How many more times and where to mix?
I wonder if I can even breathe
Not going on any longer
I'm sweating a lot, but it's okay
This is the upper limit of strength
Kotokaku doesn't work
Until you get into position
The speed is abnormal
The defeat is the key
Because I do
It's painful, my blood
技術
Because I smoked it
Cut off the stir-frying of stomach iron
Spraying at Nishi Oki
Breathing
It is dangerous in itself
Blitz and the best
Shoot the poison
In front of the spirit of the road
救減力加減
No, it was really early yesterday
The pillars that existed until now
Maybe the best of the best
Kira
Not the poison, but the neck.
I wish it had been cut
That's how fast it is.
If I had, I might have won.
Ah, that's impossible
Because you're small
Why are my hands
Is it really that small?
Why be more careful?
Didn't it grow?
Just a little bit more body
If it's big, it's the demon's neck.
Could you have cut it and defeated it?
The longer your hands and legs are, the longer
But there is also a lot of muscle mass.
So it's advantageous
My sister was a resident.
But there were more rumors than me.
Himejima-san is great
That person is coming to help
If everyone
It's reassuring.
My sister said that time
The words I was trying to say
I know
That was the end after all.
It can't be helped.
Maybe the death part will be to that demon.
I'll say I'll lose
Stop it
It was
Stay strong!
I won't allow you to cry
Sister, stand up.
Can't stand
The fertilizer from the skin is also
Cut it crisply
I can't even breathe
It doesn't matter.
The head of the samurai gang dies
If you decide to defeat them, defeat them.
Do it, I've decided to win.
If so, win.
At all costs
Winning, me and them
You promised me.
Kanao
Sorry sorry only half-heartedly
It hurts because I cut it
Shinobu will do it properly
Do your best.
oh?
picture?
Are you standing?
Are you going to stand up?
Yeah, you
Are you really human?
Sakotsu lungs and fat
Even though I cut it, your body
With that amount of bleeding
It's funny even if I'm dead
But I don't have it.
Ah, look, there's blood in your lungs.
I went in and heard a rumbling sound.
The unimaginable pain
I'll take your neck right away.
Drop it
Sorry, I'll give it to you
You can't be saved anymore
Aim without being stubborn
Then it's the neck that's the weak spot.
If you inject poison into
There is a dead
Kekokomaman?
Reverse Zaku Chabara
Move to bury dead law firing
Walking the bridge
About as much
Fast attacks are unstoppable
Low low high high
The path to happiness
Far, far away
It's still going on
I thought
Only after being destroyed
The crow whose happiness is thin
Riding on top of
I realized that it was
And we are the ones who are saved.
As if
Not yet destroyed
Someone's happiness
Become stronger
I wanted to protect
yes
Promised
Let's defeat the demons
But mostly just two people.
We share the same thoughts
I won't let anyone else
Even if the strength is weak
Even if the demon's head isn't cut off
If you defeat one demon, dozens more
If defeating is the limit
Hundreds of people
can help
Yes or no
No, I have to do it.
There are things that can't be done
He was angry.
Are you angry?
Yes, I'm angry.
Hey, Simple Road, forever.
I'm angry all the time.
Parents murdered
My sister was murdered.
Other than money
The heir was also killed.
Those kids too
If it's true, I'm still a demon
Kill the hit
If I hadn't been there, I would still be here
Family and happiness
I lived in
It really pisses me off
Don't mess with me, idiot
Why did you come here?
This guy won't do it
Idiot
You idiot, you idiot.
It was impressive. I was moved.
This weak girl
I can't believe I could do this much.
Not even better than my sister
But there are often demons
You've done it so far
That I didn't die
It's a miracle, everything is in vain
But I'll carry it through
Foolishness is the transience of humanity
The Wonder of Humanity
What is it with you? I'm in the sky
He's a terrible person forever.
Let's live together
There's something left to say
I'll ask you
Go to hell!
That idiot
I'm sure he's here
He met me too
I have to
It shouldn't be
People you love or care about
Explosively, tomorrow and the day after tomorrow
I feel like I'm still alive
It's just a wish
Only the breath of flowers
I was promised that it would definitely happen.
There is nothing
What a terrible death
Flowers in hands
Wow, that's dangerous.
Always alive and by my side
Why are some people
I thought so.
I'm going to die.
While I was absorbing it
Please don't tease me.
Oh?
This cat won't go extinct
My child just started finger spelling.
Did you do it?
My abilities
Did I teach you?
It was only for a moment, but it was amazing
Hey, it's pointless, but it's easy to try your best, I'll try my best again
I'm going to try my best.
It's easy to work hard
Well, even so
It's a beautiful night today
One after the other,
A feast is coming
Really
What a nice night
Oh?
Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
Oh?
Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
Oh? Oh?
Oh?
Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
Oh?
Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh? Other pillars and dealing with being killed
What is our situation?
Shield to death, sideways
Center of the twelve layers
The ambassador is fighting the demon.
More than a dozen
And on the back of that wall, 30
A demon that exceeds
It's approaching
Furthermore, the person's eyes,
Visualizing Blood Technology
In the eyes of those who can
The invisible art itself
This leader of light is a demon
The strength of each blood technique
It must be Sana
And pulsating
The moving sword construction
Also, the technique itself continues on and on.
What a power this is
It's an endless demon castle
We are these infinite demons
was lured into the castle
But just inviting
A Father Who Was Not Born
The party made extensive preparations,
Today has arrived
A pillar connects the life and death
Both rushed to the scene.
Promote placement so that
The Demon Slayer Ambassador who was transformed
I'm going to cut it into pieces.
Give patience to glass
Well, I waited.
Tamayosan, Yushiro
Your power is also
And to make it complete
With my parents and sisters
This battle to which I gave my life,
I won't lose
In this large space,
A great force radiates as if exerting force.
However, this
Upper limit or one of them
is the place where the death tool was
Both are the upper limit for winning!
The Upper Limit of 6 and Ambassador Agatsuma
We met
Upper limit Any other ambassadors?
not here!
There is one Agatsuma Ambassador.
Yesterday's ambassador was the limit
Strict hurry and refrain
Still the same, shorty
Great to see,
What the hell?
Have you gotten used to the pillars?
Hey, hey, all 11 of you
Other than that
Did it become?
Upper limit on appropriate hole
I put him at the bottom.
You seem very happy.
Wow
I started to say
Hey, why are you a demon?
It has become
You have the breath of Kana
The person who has a ticket for minor injury
Why did you become a demon?
You became a demon
Because of this, Sea-chan
He cut his stomach and died!
Shi-chan is
I committed suicide by myself.
Without any adaptations
When I cut my stomach, someone
I can't take your head off.
I've been suffering for a long time
die
Shi-chan will be
I can't control my throat or my heart.
And then the dead Kanna's Breath
Use the demon from
Only after you let it out!
Who cares?
So what?
sorrow?
Should I regret it?
I am the one who doesn't appreciate me
I don't care about you
Is always
Rate me correctly
What is it?
My grandfather died in agony.
If so, I'll generate it.
That much I
I did everything I could
Don't make me a spectacle
In collaboration with scum like
It's a spectacle.
That old bastard is a real old man.
Pillars or pillars
To the old man who
Because there's no use
My grandpa is senile
I didn't do it, I'm the idiot
Then you're trash.
I can only use the form
You can't use it just for the sake of appearance.
I wasn't blessed with a view.
I feel sorry for my grandpa.
No way, my name and me
Don't stare
No way, Kanai died in an emergency
The
Senzayo, trash
Cut
This guy is fast
His movements are like a different person
I'm not wrong
Kneeling before an overwhelmingly powerful person
There's no shame in that.
As long as I'm alive
It'll work out
Until I die
Not a loss
Rubbing your head on the ground
Whether you have a home or not
Drinking muddy water can make money
The theft
Even if I am insulted
As long as I'm alive
Someday we will win
I will show you, I believe, and move forward
I came here
Becoming a demon
I want more strength
You too are recognized by that person.
If we can,
Will be a companion
The stronger the swordsman, the more of a demon he becomes.
takes time
I was round
Those who can use breathing are demons.
In this case, from that person
There is a lot of blood
I must accept it.
And if you don't become a demon
Something precious
There are also
What about you?
Thank you for the blood.
To spill something
I don't understand
When you do, your neck
And the torso is sadly separated.
Every cell in that body screams
I feel like I'm going to cry.
But compared to that
Such a small thing, but a big deal
I gained the strength that I don't have.
By the way, it doesn't reach the upper limit.
Naiagatsumashite
This guy is always scum
She was crying and whimpering.
I have no strength or guts
Help me, I have a dad, I have a dad, I have a dad
There is a father
I sprained my ankle.
Together with this scum
It's a sight to behold
Shit.
Jijihore Beach
Grandpa
A little big
But with me
If you're with me
That's why
Probably not.
It's only natural that he should die.
You and your grandfather are dead.
And of course
Only one shoulder can be mastered.
I and Ichi were not there
All shoulders except
You did it!
So my grandpa is me
Together, we will fight the thunder
Breathing Spectator
I tried to
You said that
Denying it even by becoming a demon
I wanted to
Breath of Thunder, shoulder pain, everyone
In the blink of an eye
I managed to block five consecutive attacks.
Making a distinction between good and bad
It's gone now.
How can we distinguish between evil and evil?
You are the cause of the earthquake.
I guess it's your favorite
Five consecutive attacks from Grandpa
What you received
I'll put it out quickly.
What's wrong? Is the battery running out?
It's okay, I
Try hitting it
hand
Thunder Breath
First Shoulder
Enemy Attack
Stupidly honest and straightforward
Just a poke
The basic shoulder
Are you going to eat it?
Thunder Breath III
Shoulder width: 100cm
The first time while rotating
What happened to the attack?
Is it over already?
The third breath
Shoulder attack power generation
I haven't heard a single enemy attack.
Thunder Breathing Five Shoulders
The battle against the enemy has come to fruition.
It's my shoulder that's been evaluated
The sharpness cuts through skin and flesh
Crack open the drug and get rid of it
Rate me correctly
I accept that everything is low
What is not appreciated or acknowledged
I know it's bad, but this
It's my power
My own battle
Or eight-fold.
That's all you can do
But the viewer flew away
My expectations were wrong.
This is what you put out.
It's an individual
I knew it
All one now
Thunder Breathing
Sixth Shoulder
All the attacks were darkened by the bullets.
Cracks in your body
Continue to see and feel
Burn my power into you, demon
Become God
Beyond the breath
I am special
Not like you
I'm not like you guys.
Jiji's prospects are as expected
It seems that was the difference
Looking at the injury
Lick like a brother
God's breath is the best
The shoulder is the basis of all shoulders
Use only the deaf shoulder
So in the end,
Other people were able to
By the way, the big deal
Hey, but still,
The coast is
That's right, there's something on your feet
I'll tell
You're gonna die soon anyway
What are you doing, you superior?
He hit someone from his class.
Don't cause trouble, you idiot.
There are people like you
It's really a matter of taste.
The coast knows me
I hated it enough.
I knew it.
I hate the beach too
But I respect it.
From the bottom of my heart,
I was trying my best.
He was single-minded.
I'm always yours
I was looking at your back
You were special.
Grandpa and I
It's special for
He was an important person to me.
But
That's not enough
There was no such thing
I'm not happy with you at the moment.
There was a sound of
Put the happiness in your heart
There's a hole in the box
More and more happiness
Spilling out
I noticed the hole early
If it's not blocked, it won't be filled
It will never be
Grandpa
Sorry, our path is
Divided
What is the remaining capacity?
sorry
Big Brother Thunder Breathing Room
This squid is another god
You didn't run away. What happened now?
My technique is too fast
What did you use?
Damn it
It was that child-pulling
What a bastard you are!
Just tell me
I didn't tell
different
Grandpa
He's not that kind of person.
This is mine
The one I thought of, just for me
With this technique
Someday with you
Shoulder to Shoulder
I wanted to fight
The seventh technique only has six shoulders.
7 from the missing Thunder Breath
The one who created the eyes
Only one type
Someone who can't use it
He took more than me.
Win but can't stand it
I can't stand it.
The fact is
Unacceptable
I'm such a guy
Am I going to lose?
I'm going crazy
no
No, it's not a loss.
Many will fall and die.
He has no strength left.
He's gonna die with me
What you can't give to people
Someday, someone will tell me
It's not impossible to get
The guy from Hori ended up doing nothing.
It's the same as not having it
Nothing by myself
Because I can't produce
Dying Alone
That's the second one.
Here,
Jay-chan
Sorry, I'm friends with the beach.
I couldn't
I also wrote letters.
Reply
Please don't do it
If I wasn't here, the beach
I hope it doesn't turn out like that.
There may not have been
Forgive me for being a man and don't give me anything in return
I can't do it Jay
Chan is alive
There was a thundering sound on the pillars of my house.
I wanted to
Sorry Jay
Sorry
She started to hate me
Say something
Jay-chan
It's filthy
This is tangled up in my legs
Jay-chan
This is ridiculous
Somehow everyone
You are my pride
You, you, you
You you you you you you you you you you you you you you
You, you are noisy
Shut up, Murata Mitaka
Don't be attacked by money
Look around carefully
You!
What is the coast like?
If it were a person, it would be
I won't.
I'm a demon, so I go to the beach
Who knows?
I use a blood thinner
These scars and cracks on my face
If it doesn't stop, eyeballs
I'll avoid it until
Can you hear me?
Scary things for the weak
Don't say that, and the blood poison too.
I'm using it but the bleeding hasn't stopped.
No, stop it!
It's absolutely fine!
I will definitely help!
You're not gonna die!
Good luck, Amesuma!
keep it up!
The upper limit you were fighting at
I still have my own skills and abilities.
I couldn't use it properly.
Luckily there is one battle
If it happened a year later, he would die instantly.
That must have been the case.
Email words
Absolutely not!
I did it wrong
I didn't say that!
What's that? You're yelling.
The demon has come
Nice window, hey!
Hey!
Did you say Yushirou?
Agatsuma is
I'll ask you to do it!
Please kill him quickly
Hey senpai!
I learned that later!
Fuck!
Water Breathing,
The second waterwheel!
Is that a fish pond?
Because it goes around
Go that way!
oh?
Bad encounter
No upper limit encountered
The place where Muzan is is still
Is it far away?
Is everyone still safe?
Shinobu
I'm sure we'll win.
surely
Everyone is us
What?
This shaking is Kiyuu!
stop!
Calm down!
Is someone fighting again?
Someone else dies
Will it happen?
No, it's not.
It's coming closer
Ugh, this smell
Up!
30!
More!
How rude
I'm glad I was alive.
A weakling like you
Umm, umm, Tanjiro!
Yay!
Probably the mayonnaise on this meat.
Among things like
Decomposing the drug that turns you back into a human
They're probably breaking down the drug that turns them back into humans in the mayonnaise-like substance in the meat.
Maybe the drug that turns them back into humans is being broken down in this meaty mayonnaise.
I'm so sad.
You are the only one
We must not allow the village to be abandoned.
And yet
No matter what
Gisul: Me too.
Captured
please
Someone come quickly
please!
My father thinks so.
If he dies, the other demons will die too.
Then the spirit is splendid.
Still alive
The power of mercy is the Tama budget
Suppressed by
There must be something to suppress.
I can't say that
In Yushiro's eyes
The cruel power of not reacting
What will happen before the resurrection?
Even if you defeat
Must have
But this
In the infinite castle
Truly a pitiful and tragic experience.
Finding
Is it possible?
Don't rush
You're doing well
He always shows up
At my place
would have come too
What is "Kibuddha and miserable"?
That's the kind of guy he is.
My father
I will definitely accomplish it.
Before our power runs out
Find and settle
If you don't add
Stand up, we'll work hard
The pillars are stretched out
Stay in the grassland
Please go ahead.
Inoue Shiro, hurry up you guys
Definitely beat the boss
Please
please
I get it, this is you
Leave it to us, Tokushima
Damn it, Pillar Gamer
Show the world
Just what?
thank you
Father, everyone is stubborn.
It's been stretched out
Father, I want to know about you guys.
Mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother, mother
Mother Mother Mother Mother Mother
MotherFatherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMotherMother
Mother, I suffered because I had to protect you.
It seems like
I cooperated with my parents
It's called Tamayo
The medicine that the demon laid down
I used it as instructed
I can't see something I can't see something I can't see something I can't see something I can't see something I can't see something I can't see something
Demons that don't disappear in sunlight
In these long years
Nezuko alone
The term "final stage"
I have been
It crosses my mind
Every time that happened, my body trembled.
Increased heart rate
This long battle is tonight
It may end
I can't believe I'm there.
To stand alive
Feel it, you're the devil
My sister who became
From the time I brought you
Something big is happening
It started to spin.
I feel like
The images accumulated in the past battles
What was created was a huge device
If so, then you and
Two types of "Nezuko"
A small Haguruma
I got hooked and now I can't
The situation that was
It started moving at once
Don't give up, Nezuko
Don't give up, Tanjiro
Don't lose to the whole
It's a bloody hair horn, Kacchan!
GO!
I can't even cut my arm!
I can't cut off his head!
Disappeared
Effective in attacking as well
Aim for the neck that can fight
No, but next
The hair on the arm is now
Arm hair cornersArm hair corners
Arm hair angle arm
Nokamikaze Tanjiro
The skill is refined in the expansion
It is being raised
Your abilities are a pillar.
It is no exaggeration to say that
Not the upper limit of Sam
I was so grateful to the other person that day.
Despair in the trees, Kobe
With tears dripping down my face, my sister
The only way to save his life is to
You who were not there
Now I can fight
Robbery of life and dignity
To avoid being
This boy is not weak.
Don't insult me, Professor.
The words were right.
I'll admit it, you are
It wasn't weak.
Show your respect
術式展開
Let's get started
It's time for Kakage
You, you, you, you, you, you, you
You, you, you
You you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you
You
You, you, you
You you you you you you you you you you you
You, you
You, you, you
You you you you you you you you you you you you you you
You, you
You, you, you
You, you, you, you, you, you, you
You, you
Your Queen
Let's get started
107 Yongsan Naval Port
Geezer!
Is that right?
Geezer
Is that the name?
Kagura the Tree God!
Destruction!
Die!
Let's become a shooter!
Geezer!
Good move!
It's amazing how quickly this place has been built.
I visited
I'll give you a compliment!
Even so, Professor
You did a great job.
That night I fell to the ground.
You were waiting
Only the overwhelmingly weak weeds
No, but guess what!
You are amazing now
Growth, I am pure
My happy heart is dancing!
Professor that night
I'm glad I died
If you think about it, it's even better than that.
I couldn't become stronger
A human who may be
It's nonsense that
Values
I had it.
What?
You, shut up now
Mr. Hayashiki
Don't talk!
Why am I being invited away?
There you are
And Professor Otoko is different too.
You are immature
Just spitting out the grains
I'm just here for anyone
Or to anyone
It was a misunderstanding, I'm just a idiot.
What I hate is the weak.
I spit out the grains
Only the weak can make calls
Only for weaklings
There is a ignore diagram
Running Equality
What is ejected is natural
Nothing but a cut
What you're saying
It's all wrong.
You are there now
That's the proof.
At birth, everyone
A weak baby, to someone
I need help.
You can't live either
That's right baby
Maybe I don't remember
But when I was a baby
You are being protected by someone
Now I'm saved
I'm alive
The strong help the weak
Protect and the weak are strong
Also, I'm more
Helping and protecting the weak
But it's natural that I'm a baby.
I forgive your way of thinking.
No more of yours
I won't let you like me
got it
I put this in the center of my body.
So I don't accept it.
Even though I've become stronger, I'm still deep
The feeling won't go away
Whatever you do
At first, everyone is impressed
With help from those around me
I'm the one who remembers others
I'm comparing the two live.
No, it's an opponent
is always yourself
What's important is who you were yesterday
It's about becoming stronger
This continues for 10 or 20 years.
If we can do that, it will be a great
And now
You are a person
I'll shine a light on you
What?
In the middle of nowhere
I shook it off.
Simple
You are deep after all
The biggest war in the early stages of development
It's too early.
Rather than looking fast, this
This feeling, this personality
This is a re-kill
I was expecting
Quick Loot
Several times, the action was previewed.
Even if you can withstand the attack
Too much power and no compensation
The personality that can't reduce it to zero
A safe rush of moves
As sure as possible
Let me shove it.
Towards the rapidity of the body
The incoming attack is absorbed into the self-fire area.
It has been sent
It's like, what?
What is it?
What does it react to and attract?
You can do it.
You think first
It was something
The past of Akatan Kendo
If you smoke
Wide-screen camera
Put on Keen
It's an interesting technique.
The feeling of being worried grew
What does it look like?
Did you swing it that way?
The shoreline sways like a shadow child.
That's interesting.
Wooden Hair Kagura Pencil
Damn
Come
Separate each other
Let go let go
No, I won't let go
Barely
I'm so mad
My back hurts without doing anything.
How far can you fly?
Thank you for that.
Upper limit sushi
I really want to pull out my sword.
No, it doesn't matter who it is
A match like five losses
I don't like to do it either
But now I am overwhelmed.
With a strong man for the first time in a while
The feeling was immediate after meeting
Sharply entangled
I realized that
The closed sensation hits
Being pulled up and dragged
To the place where the strong stand
Barely alive
The thing called a deal
How much of a person's ability
I understood how to stretch
Barely
Asakawa Discovery
That thing went up
Zamaton Breathes Water
Let's shoot the other one.
Key Head
Barely
Just barely
Both are just barely early.
But Girigiri-san
The increased speed immediately turned red
Sa is a pure idol
Barely
Your power is
Is that outrageous?
Just barely
Barely
More
Shoot me some more
Barely watery shoulders and buttocks
Point water shoulder water shoulder water bottom water no
Point destruction dance gya
It's barely red.
Calm down
Think about it, don't rush, absolutely
Don't abandon enforcement
Why is it so red?
The attack is magnetic
How accurate is it?
Attacking from behind or from the corners
Why do we always react to
Think
The head and legs are trained
The current enforcement
Close to the region of
Red in the fight against United Nations
The head and legs
I used the word
What is a head and foot? I smell
Various things
Redness so you can feel it
Something with the head and legs
I feel
The enemy made just the slightest advance.
The target is
So Inotsuki
Gyutaro's attack
I noticed you behind me.
It was from
But it's amazing
I have a strong body skin.
From behind.
But someone is watching me
Hey, I know you're watching.
Give it a try
Let me do it.
Look at your right shoulder
What a win!
Look into the distance
The one who comes is a one shot
I understand, but I don't understand
It's so fast
Just now, I was touching the skin of my body.
Sagusa stinger
Here it comes
That's right, the moon in the well is also melted and piled up.
The sensation of touching your skin
What is invisible to
What happened after that?
I talked about
At that time
However, on the other hand,
I realized that he was a man without a time limit.
It can be difficult.
That little papa
The mouth of a flower
The pabber at home
It was scary.
Before you know it
Grab a handful of rice and
I was sitting in the back
Don't say pabar
No, grandma.
Pabba-san, caller, me
I thought so just now.
If you approach without noticing
Then kill him.
If you don't have one, don't have one.
But that's Grandma
I feel sorry for the moon
I want to add
Because there wasn't
Without bringing up the previous demon
To defeat
I don't think it's possible
Well, that's true.
Not the same as before
It's a blow to the gut.
The head of the family is
It's beautiful.
Trivial conversation
But I was sure of something.
On
I feel like
The Chinese character for redness
What is a scalp that
Is it different from before?
Willingness to try
Time or amount
With my scent
Something like a mover
The Battle of Red
How to make it crazy
Kaoshi's hair
Video Zaraki
That's right, Tanjiro
yes
Exciting
Bankan Chi just now impossible
The realm of thought, huh?
That's it
Ohohoe
Look, my dad has sunburn
What happens when you dance the Kagura?
I'm thinking
If Dad is in pain
If so, I'll be the one next year.
Dad's body will change
Thank you I'm worried
Even though I'm just kidding, my father
In recent years, Kagura
tough
I have never thought
It's a strange thing.
Grandpa Kagura
When I first learned
Younger, healthier and stronger
I couldn't even hold my breath
sea bream
It was painful to become
Once a year at the beginning of the year
The sickle has been gone for many generations.
Kitakagura starts from sunset
Until dawn
Continuing hardship
It was something like that.
There are a total of 12 dance styles
Hundreds and thousands of
Repeat a thousand times
30 people wasted movement
There were a lot
The last thing I want to do is
Correct breathing and correct
Movement: First movement
exert maximum force
So what?
My mind is gradually becoming clearer
It becomes
transparent?
I can't remember at first.
The movements that must be made
Don't pick up the feeling
must
Open the compatibility of your body
Recognizing the shape of each individual blood vessel
This time is really painful
Continue struggling like this
I'm stuck in a dead end
I can only imagine that
I remember a lot of things
After absorption, it is necessary
Suck away what is not there
What is needed for the movement
Just leave
Close close?
When people try to listen carefully, people try to listen carefully.
Close your eyes when
That's how it is.
What is most needed at that moment
Choose something
It's coming, soon all over my body
Opening of blood vessels and muscles
Blink Close
So quick and easy
Be able to
At that moment, light appeared.
The way to stab opens
Inside my head, inside my head
The world becomes clear when you
But
This is as much as we can
Because I suffered
I have finally reached that realm
Can I go there?
Continue your efforts without saying too much.
Banana Hollow
Thank you
10 days before my father died
Bears attack and eat people
One incident
It happened on the mountain over there
Spread the sun around the house
The name with the lines is
It was spread all over
Short life
yes
Follow me
Yep, see?
The one who is hungry is
I'm sorry, but more than that
Come here
I will not tolerate
I feel good about my family.
How many people are there?
I will not tolerate delinquency.
If you don't listen to the warning
Taking a life
It is intended to
As thick as a human torso
The bear has a bell around its neck.
With the roots
It fell with a thud
I couldn't follow it with my eyes
But maybe my father is a mabataki
Twice during
I think it was cut
Otherwise, that
Cut off the head with the width of an axe
It is impossible
My father's scent doesn't waver at all
The bear's neck was missing.
No fear before or after cutting
Without lunch
I haven't released it yet
Did you see it properly?
Don't forget what you just saw
My father used his power
Mischievously alluring
Not a person
I realized later
That is a show of talent.
He let me
I can see the transparent world
From my father's great judgment
So that I can learn
My dad and my grandpa
And Grandpa Hinomi
Surely the same
Never give up
Keep going, no matter what obstacles
Someday
Overcoming it with the efforts of many horses
I know, Dad.
So that time, the redness
Those late afternoons
exchanged blows.
Maybe that blow was mine.
Complete life
It was something to be stolen.
Change with Giwoo
A change of technique
Rapidly gaining recognition
From a blow like that
Please protect me.
But at that moment
Even Giu-san can be in between.
Didn't fit
But maybe it's impossible
I couldn't do it at that time.
For some reason I didn't think
I only felt it for a moment
I put it in for just a moment.
That World
A world that penetrates
The body seemed to penetrate
Hantenkyuu in my heart
When I was hiding
was the same
Did you see it or did you buy it?
I don't know
Focus only on the meeting
And the other senses were closed.
I still can't win
It moved quickly
My dad taught me that.
I entered a world that penetrates
Time prediction and attack
Speed increases exponentially
The movement of the opponent's blood vessels
Flow and contraction
See through
The contraction of your own muscles
Faster
I knew the name
Red is probably simply
Headphones closed
Aim for the neck with
Might be
Figure it out
Now all the water is gone.
It seems like you've given it your all. Enough already. Let's end it here.
I was brought in and got off
I'll put it down, I won't avoid it
Punching
moreover
End attack mid-arm
What does it mean to cut it off and stop it?
The sound of breathing
Maybe not.
Simply saved
All the cells in the body are born
Right now,
He is telling me to kill
This guy has some
A change has occurred
It's dangerous
He simply
Concentrated
attack
術式展開術
式大銀欄斬行
Also, the speed of the attack
The rising power is increasing
Why can I accept it?
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Combat Combat Combat Combat Technique
Time passes slowly
no
Movement slows down
Can you see it?
It's deep
I saw 200 shots almost at the same time.
Even with the strike, everything is in vain
Justice was not achieved
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
Battle Battle Battle
No, there's no problem.
Even an attack will destroy me.
Shin is the one who feels
The stronger the fighting, the stronger
About Racing
The reaction only gets stronger
What is this strange thing?
There is something else going on
It seems to have become a living thing
This guy has stopped moving.
Uh, there's no movement.
What to do when you come to Nagawa
Strengthening Angel
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
battle
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
BattleBattle
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Battle Battle Battle
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
Battle Battle Battle Battle
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
Battle Battle Battle
battle
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Battle Battle Battle Battle
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
Battle Battle Battle
Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat Combat
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
Battle Battle Battle
Oh no...
It's a sturdy one.
I threw so much into the battle
And without any anti-nationalism,
To wake up.
In combat, I am lightly constructed.
Soryuu, a stalk
A martial arts comrade who fights in
Are they doing it?
One Kado family member
Don't bark.
Like Vendya
By doing this, Hidehime was brought home
It is made.
I want you to do it first.
What hurts is,
It's the Second Hand Girl's official illness.
I have a job
So, I want to leave it to you.
The other day, my wife was diagnosed with government disease.
So he committed suicide by gunfire.
It's so hard.
This is it.
I am truly harmless.
Because of this, my wife and daughter
To cause trouble.
A wealthy man in a house with only one daughter
Put me
Is it okay to be there?
You, the wealthy man, are in the Sengoku period.
I want to beat you up
Because I put it on.
It's okay.
They look similar.
I see.
You're so uncomfortable
It was like this
Get rid of your boring past
to make
That's what it was.
This is my daughter, Koyuki.
A stupid past.
Stupid.
Sorry, Shiroshi.
What do you think, Koyuki?
Is it okay to wake up?
She's definitely cuter than in the morning
It's getting better.
Maybe it's a little better.
Ah, this one.
No matter how many times I ask, he never says his name.
Hey, don't tell anyone.
Sit here.
Well, until I get back.
Ask
Leave it there.
Umm... face...
Is your hair okay?
I'm sure it will heal.
Help, protect.
My life is an adventure
Just a mess
Stupid
It was something like that.
thank you.
Don't tell me every single thing
That's fine.
Sleep without worrying
Please.
sorry.
Sorry for the trouble.
That's fine.
Should we close this place? It's fine as it is.
Koyuki is really
I was weak.
All night long,
A towel to help those affected by the disaster
Hey, change your pajamas.
Or drink water to the beans.
Of course, I had to carry him when we went to Kawaya.
Koyuki was really weak. When we went to Kawaya,
Of course I have to carry it.
It had to be.
Originally, I was my father’s
I was sick with a government illness.
Extraordinary heart
Because my body was able to function,
It's not very spicy.
I'm always sorry.
People who suffer from illness,
Why always apologize?
Taking the time to
I'm sorry.
The coughing is loud
Unable to work satisfactorily
I'm sorry.
Take care of yourself
I would like to.
My cough won't stop
It doesn't exist.
If you can breathe normally
I would like to.
The most painful thing is the person
But it should be.
I'm always sorry.
Because of me, the single
I can't,
I can't even go play.
I want to play
I don't think so.
Since long ago.
Around the time we met
Since I'm doing a single bet,
Do not do so.
But sometimes I feel
Tonight there will be fireworks to celebrate the change
Because it seems to be rising,
Go ahead.
I agree.
Eyes and eyebrows converge
If you wait,
Carrying it on my back, to the front of the bridge
Shall we go?
If you can't go today,
Next year too, the fireworks will
It will rise, so go at that time.
That's fine.
The only troublesome thing about government illnesses
I thought so because of the conversation
On the way, light snow started falling
Wake up
It was crying.
I'm in a sickbed
Maybe, but it's not bad.
When I get it, I can't help it
To become unkind.
I see.
Is this the white in Shiroji?
Is that a pony?
I see.
You are definitely
Just like me.
If there's nothing to protect
It's no good.
A child protecting his mother
That's something like that.
Not a samurai or anything, just a commercial product
But with such a large amount of land
Has soil
The old man was attacked by the mountain tribe.
I helped him out of his misery.
However, the old man
I was deeply moved by Ryu's technique.
And, soon
The land of the past and the old
The soil was sold commercially.
Apparently so.
But the land and
The soil is ours
Those who wanted to
It's not interesting.
The sword-fighting ground that was established was
In soluble soil
They were harassing me.
Because of that, Soryu
Soil has cultural value
did not increase.
However, the training here
Koyuki's official illness,
My heart was saved.
Three years later, I
turned 18.
Koyuki is 16 and can be a bit flustered.
Almost gone,
To be able to live normally
It had become.
White background, right?
yes.
You see, this soil
Follow
Or white background?
Hey, Shiroji, you too, Koyuki.
I like
That's what I'm saying.
teeth?
The financial statement has already been submitted
My future is in
What a good imagination!
I couldn't.
And what's more, someone
Follow that self
A future that gives
What, even better.
Maybe I,
My dad said
So, from now on
The right way to live
Can it be done?
You can start your life over
It may be
A faint hope, but a collection
As much as
It swells up big.
At this time, I was in awe of my life.
I want to protect it no matter what
The two people who thought that were killed
etc.
I never dreamed it would happen.
Visit the grave
It was my dad's.
Report that the collection limit will be increased
I want to, and the sun sets
Before, I had sympathy.
Even though I returned,
I vomited before I even heard it.
it was.
The large curtain is light and I don't like it.
I get goosebumps at this premonition
was standing there.
It's gotten bigger. It's gotten bigger. It's gotten bigger. It's gotten bigger. It's gotten bigger. It's gotten bigger.
Someone in the well
I put one in.
Makeup umbrella and you directly
Even if we fight, we can't win
So, those guys are terrible.
Until now, without a song
Too much, but small
Even Chan was killed.
I have a loved one in danger
When you are suffering from
He's not always there.
Someone important to me is in danger.
I know someone important to me is in danger. The little person knows someone important to me is in danger.
Tiny humans in danger
is being hit.
I have a loved one in danger.
is suffering from.
Someone important to me is in danger.
I will continue to
I am still alive
The future is well imagined
It was not possible.
I had a hard time imagining my future, even in old age.
I couldn't imagine myself living a long life, much less the present one. My mother felt the same way.
So, I'm dying.
I don't want to see it, I'll kill myself
I did.
I'm sure my father, too,
Are you giving up somewhere?
but,
I knew it.
I said too much.
Too much, but...
To you, my future
But I could see it.
Of course
So, the year, and even
Talk about the year
It was possible.
I was really happy.
I am White
It's better.
Me and Meoto
Would you be willing?
yes.
I am stronger than anyone
Become a part of your life
I will protect you.
In the end, it was all lip service.
Nothing
I couldn't.
What?
Yay! It's Bray!
Damn it, soryo!
After I was murdered,
Gate of Survival Mars
One person can hide their swordsmanship.
Attack on the dojo.
It killed 67 people.
The method is already
Head destruction,
Destroys internal organs.
Most of the pain is caused by crushing
There was no sign of anything dangerous happening.
Finished and part of the body
However, the result was severe damage.
Now, the jaw, the brain, the eyeballs,
Limbs, general, ceiling
Splashing on the call wall
To Hell!
The deciding factor is Kamiba.
Not human!
I remember worshiping the demon.
A demon appeared in a place that didn't exist
To the king of
When I went there,
Just a human being.
How boring.
Get out of the way, you're killed.
Just like this.
About twelve strong demons.
do
I'm thinking about it.
You can give this
The amount of blood
Can you stand it?
yes.
It doesn't matter right now.
Everything...
Becoming a demon and losing your memory
And I
I sought strength.
queue!
More!
Shoot some more!
What I wanted to protect
There's nothing left now
I say no.
In a world where I've lost my family,
I wanted to live
But that's not the case.
Over a century of senseless killing
Repeat the force,
Oh my goodness, rainbow eyes
So, in terms of national origin,
That's a boring story.
When I died, I was with three people.
Same place
I can't go.
I was reminded of that.
What a past.
Human name, or
A fragile weakling!
Dies quickly, breaks down, disappears
It's gone!
Not yet dead
No, that's ridiculous!
I have to do it now.
When played here,
There's no turning back now!
It was during the battle!
The head, the head regenerates
It's happening!
I cut off his head!
Red murder, Meshiki, Yagara!
Is this one still moving?
Cut off your head as many times as you want!
We can win!
With Giryu
Red Tani in style!
In style, Red Kill,
Eyelids, yagara!
Red murder, Meshiki, Yagara!
Red murder, blindfold, yagara! Red murder, blindfold, yagara!
I hate weak people!
The weak ones, raw,
Noble, no fighting, thread
Poison it!
Hard to see!
The weak one,
Not enough mandrels!
Soon it will be time to protect yourself!
Protective Ignorance
And killed someone!
Tsukasa's precious solution
Covered in rice, my father
We can't even protect our rights!
That's right, I
I wanted to kill him...
Why why why!
The winner flew away!
I hit him.
Then it won't stop!
Combat is impossible!
Fighting is impossible! Fighting is impossible! The redness is in Rengoku-san's hands.
Let's take out the used mats
This is what they say!
Bring along Giriyu
Attack unseen!
Don't mind me!
If you don't kill me...
I hate weak people!
Combat is impossible!
By myself, by myself…
Me…
Why me?
Did you attack?
Why…
For a moment, redness turned to gratitude.
It smelled.
Why did you laugh?
Enough!
Stop it!
Don't play!
The game is over!
I've lost!
At that moment, I was toast!
Generated, dignified,
It was a brilliant move!
Perfect your enemy's movements
Read and rotate at the last minute!
The enemy launches an attack.
Cut forward!
It's over!
Poorly,
I want to go to hell...
Where to go
Do you want to?
My feet stopped...
Dad...are you okay now?
Isn't it painful?
It's okay, white people...
Thank you...
Sorry, Dad...
Sorry, I'll try again
There was no… no good.
It was... it has nothing to do with that...
How are you?
Well, a son is a son...
A disciple is a disciple...even in death
I won't abandon you...
There are many places in Japan.
I can't go, but...
Shia... I want to become stronger
Wasn't it...?
This is you
Is this the end...?
Redness...
That's right... I'm strong
I want to become stronger...
Because I was cut from the group
What... a contest?
It doesn't matter...Kill them all.
I'll do it...I'm still strong
I promise...
If we don't protect it...
oh…
White child...
thank you…
Enough already...
That's enough...
Enough already...red!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry... Protect me
Sorry I wasn't there... with the Ambassador
Sorry I don't smoke...
No matter how many promises you keep,
I didn't... I forgive you.
Y-You forgave me.
Please...forgive me...
About us... About you... About you
About you guys...
Thank you for aiming for me
It was... the original Shiraji
Return to
I'm glad...
Welcome back... Shiroji...
Yo!
White child!
Welcome back!
White baby...White baby...White baby...
I'm home…
I'm back...
welcome home…
you…
oh…
Gone...
It's over...
Hurry...Next...Tamayosan
In...the place...
Rather than relying on...
Don't rely on me... Don't rely on me...
I'd rather rely on you... I'd rather rely on you... I'd rather rely on you... I'd rather rely on you... I'd rather rely on you... I'd rather rely on you... I'd rather rely on you... I'd rather rely on you...
Rather than relying on... relying on
Rather... more reliable...
Rather than trusting... Akazano...
The benefits are gone...
Ashiki yuд...
Akaza... Will you defeat me?
Wasn't it...?
Further insight
Opening the way to
Abandoning nature
How many thousand?
Akazad's Maybe
Are you dead?
For a moment, I felt strange.
But it's just my imagination.
Akazad or something else
Death becomes a living thing
So now it's Axie, Axie
Because he's dead
I don't know
Umm, what was it again?
Oh, that's right.
Ask your name
There was
AxiAxiAxiAxi
Sea Axi Axi
Sea axi axi
Axiaki
Sea axis
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Sea Axi Axi Axi Axi Axi
Sea axis
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Axiaxi
Sea axi axi
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Axiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxia
Axiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxia
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Sea axi axi
Axiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxii
Axiaxiaxiaxiaxi
Axiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxia
Sea axi axi
Axiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxia
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Sea axis
Sea axi axi
Axiaxiaxiaxiaxiaxii
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Sea axi axi
Sea axis
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Sea Axi Axi Axi Axi Axi Axi
Sea axi axi
Axiaxiaxiaxiaxi
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Sea axi axi
Sea Axi Axi Axi Axi Axi Axi
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Sea axi axi
Axiaki
Sea axis
Axiaxiaxiaxi
Sea axi axi