Muzan will come someday.
Please, use me as bait to take Muzan's head.
Why do you think that way?
I just feel it.
There's no logic to it. The other children
wouldn't agree to using me as bait.
This is a mission I can only entrust to you.
That man won't die even if you cut off his head.
I believe the only thing that can destroy Muzan is sunlight.
Even if you destroy his head and he doesn't die, it'll become a battle to hold him off until sunrise.
Giyuu!
If that's your request,
Thank you.
I pray that no more of my precious children will die.
So, you thought you could corner me like this?
You're all headed to hell.
You annoying Demon Slayers!
Tonight, I'll make you all my prey!
The ones going to hell are you demons!
I won't let you escape!
Let's do this.
If you can.
Tanjiro Kamado!
Defeat them!
Muzan must fall!
Where am I?
Everything's upside down and all over the place!
Is the enemy's castle
a constructed space?
I can't grasp the situation.
Tanjiro was fighting so fiercely.
But...
I don't know how long he can keep it up.
Calm down, Zenitsu!
Y-Yes!
Stay close!
Ugh...
Ah...
AHHH!
There!
You'll be crushed to death!
Unleash your technique and cut through to the core!
There's something controlling this building!
My footing is bad.
It's hard to brace myself against the fall!
The whole thing...
is at a vanishing distance!
You see the darkness
Shake your head
Like a light
Leave all the mirrors
To the moon
Ha, ha, ha!
Are you okay?
Yes, thank you!
You saved me!
Water Breathing, Flowing Dance!
Everyone, come on!
This game...
Hmm...
Giyuu-san is incredible!
He reads my slightest movements and predicts my techniques!
Then he counters with his own techniques, moving so we don't clash!
This guy is unreal!
What's with that smug look?!
Nnnn...
This must be...
the demon's stronghold that Shinazugawa and Iguro mentioned.
If so, Kibutsuji's goal in gathering us here is to wipe out the Demon Slayer Corps, including the Hashira.
From here on, we must be even more vigilant.
Yes!
Let's go!
Like this...
Where's Oyakata-sama?
He was caught in a moment of carelessness.
It was the end for him.
That man...
I can't believe he'd make a mistake that would let a demon find him.
To sacrifice himself...
Exactly.
There was no way to avoid it.
Oyakata-sama was always encouraging me when I was attacked by a demon and my mind was on the brink.
The other Hashira were doing the same at that moment.
Like a father.
Yes, I know.
Muzan took not only my brother but our father as well.
Damn you, Muzan!
I'll slaughter you! I'll send you to hell!
Rest assured.
We all feel the same.
Oyakata-sama...
We couldn't protect him.
Stupid
Hell yeah!
What is this place?
My Nezuko and the others...
Big brother...
Please, big brother, stay alive!
I heard a sound...
That guy might be nearby.
I smell blood.
Where am I?
Demon Slayers...
Quit the Demon Slayer Corps.
You're trying so hard,
really trying so hard,
but you'll probably die fighting Muzan.
Live a normal girl's life and find happiness.
I want you to live until you're an old lady.
You've done enough.
No!
I absolutely won't quit!
I'll definitely take down Muzan!
Tell me!
What kind of demon was it?
Who killed her?
Himejima-san! Tell me!
Please!
To have this happen...
I can't live with such injustice!
Himejima-san!
It was a demon covered in blood from head to toe.
Hey there.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Douma.
It's a nice night, isn't it?
Smiling brightly without a care.
Speaking calmly and gently.
Help... Help!
Help!
Shh... I'm talking, aren't I?
Hm?
Are you okay?
Whoa! You're fast!
Are you a Hashira?
Oh, don't worry! Just leave them there; I'll eat them properly later.
Here you go.
When you use those bones, they're sharp and precise.
I am the leader of the Eternal Paradise Cult.
My goal is to bring happiness to everyone in the cult.
I'll eat that child cleanly, without leaving anything behind.
This is the demon who killed my sister!
Everyone's happiness, you ruined it!
That person was begging for help!
So I saved her, didn't I?
That child is no longer in pain,
no longer suffering, no longer afraid.
That's why I'm eating her.
She'll live on with me.
For eternity.
I take the feelings of the believers,
their blood and flesh, and save them,
guiding them to a higher plane.
You don't seem sane.
Is your head okay?
You make me sick.
Ugh...
Oh, I see. Poor thing. You must have gone through something painful.
Let me listen. Tell me about it.
Pain? There's no such thing! You killed my sister!
Don't you recognize this haori?!
My breathing is stopping.
I can't see it yet.
That's some pull.
I couldn't stop it with my hands.
Repel technique!
Puzzle High-Con!
So strong...
High-Lostack is getting overwhelmed.
Fast, so fast!
But it's just brute force.
You can't save your sister with raw power.
The neck!
I have to cut the neck!
You can't kill with strength alone, but what about me?
Let's see if this poison works on an Upper Rank.
Sister, please...
Sister...
This poison is stronger than the one used on Rui's mountain.
As expected, information was shared.
The poison is extremely potent.
They're adapting the information for each demon.
That man was lost too...
This is fun!
Eating poison is so interesting!
I'm getting addicted!
Think the next mix will work?
Let's try it!
Right.
Sounds good.
Well...
This was within expectations.
Is the talk over?
Come at me anytime.
I said try it,
but the same technique is boring.
Slower than before, huh?
Like this...
Pure white hair is a sign of innocence.
This child is special.
She must hear the voice of God.
My parents' stupidity was hopeless.
Otherwise,
they wouldn't have created such a dull religion as the Eternal Paradise Cult.
I felt sorry for them,
so I always played along.
I never once heard the voice of God.
At first,
I was worshipped and prayed to by everyone,
and it honestly troubled me.
Children came crying to me,
saying they were suffering, in pain.
Adults would ask me what to do,
and I worried if their heads were okay.
After telling me their tragic life stories,
they'd bow and beg me to guide them to paradise.
I cried.
Poor things.
Paradise doesn't exist.
It's a fairy tale humans made up in their delusions.
Neither God nor Buddha exists.
These people, living for decades,
can't understand such a simple truth.
When you die, you become nothing.
You feel nothing.
Your heart stops,
your brain stops,
and you rot back into the earth.
That's the fate of all living things.
They can't accept such a simple truth.
Being stupid is painful, isn't it?
I want to make these pitiful people happy.
I want to save them. That's why I
was born.
Fifth try... no good. It didn't work.
It's becoming less effective. How many more times can you mix poison?
Oh, you're out of breath. Sweating a lot. You okay?
This is the strength of an Upper Rank.
The poison isn't working at all.
Its resistance builds up abnormally fast!
The poison is starting to affect you.
Tough, huh? You inhaled my Blood Demon Art earlier.
Argh! No way! You're too small!
Why are my hands so small?
Why didn't I grow taller?
If I were just a bit bigger,
could I have cut off the demon's head and defeated it?
The longer your arms and legs, the more muscle you have,
giving you an advantage.
My sister was small, but she was stronger than me.
Himejima-san is amazing. If he came to help, everyone would feel safe.
The words my sister would have said at that moment...
I know them.
Is this really the end?
No choice, huh?
The Demon Slayers will probably lose to that demon.
She told me to give up.
Get a grip!
I won't forgive crying!
Sister, stand up!
I can't stand. I'm exhausted.
My throat is slashed, and I can barely breathe.
That doesn't matter. Stand up!
Insect Hashira, Shinobu Kocho!
If you decide to defeat it, defeat it. If you decide to win, win!
Win at any cost, with me and Kanao.
That's what we promised, right?
Kanao...
Sorry, sorry. It hurts because I only half-cut it, right?
The Demon Slayers can do it properly. Keep going!
You're standing? Really standing? Wow!
Are you really human?
Your collarbone, lungs, and fat are cut,
and with your size and that amount of blood loss, you should be dead.
Listen! There's blood in your lungs, making gurgling sounds!
That must be unimaginable pain!
I'll quickly cut off your head,
so don't push yourself.
You can't be saved anymore, so don't be stubborn.
If you're going to aim, go for the vital point—the neck.
If you can drive poison into the neck, there's still a chance.
Insect Breathing,
like this...
Huh?
A chaotic mess!
"Movements buried in the firing of death."
"An aura strong enough to split a bridge."
So fast... I can't read the attacks...
So low...
The path to happiness...
I believed it stretched on forever and ever.
Only when it was destroyed did I realize that happiness was resting on fragile glass.
And just as we were saved,
I wanted to grow stronger to protect someone else's unbroken happiness.
That's right, we made a promise.
Yes, we promised.
To defeat the demons.
Together, to take down as many as we can.
So that no one else has to feel the same pain we did.
Even if our strength is weak,
even if we can't cut a demon's neck, defeating just one demon could save dozens of people.
If we can defeat an Upper Rank, we could save hundreds of people.
It's not about whether we can do it.
It's about what we must do.
Are you angry?
Yes, I'm angry.
Tanjiro-kun, I've been angry for a long, long time.
My parents were killed. My sister was killed.
Even Kanao's fellow Tsuguko were killed.
Those girls,
if they were still alive,
if they hadn't been killed by demons,
they'd be living happily with their families.
It really pisses me off.
Don't screw with me, you bastard!
Why isn't the poison working on this guy?!
You damn idiot!
The foolishness of persevering despite everything being futile.
That's the fragility of humans, and the beauty of humans.
You're someone who makes me feel uplifted.
Let's live together forever.
Any last words?
I'll listen.
Go to hell.
Master!
He's definitely here somewhere.
That guy has to face me, no matter what.
Loved ones and precious people...
You vaguely feel they'll be alive tomorrow, the day after.
But that's just a wish.
Flower Breathing!
There's no such thing as an absolute promise.
Fourth Form!
Crimson Hanagoromo!
Phew, that was close, close!
They're always alive, by my side.
For some reason, people tend to believe that.
Don't get in the way while I'm absorbing them.
Oh?
You didn't fall for the bait.
Did this kid just use sign language earlier?
Did she tell you about my abilities?
In just a moment, that's impressive.
But it's pointless.
Such a hard worker, huh?
Man, even so,
tonight is a great night.
One fine feast after another keeps coming.
Ah, truly,
a wonderful night.
You're there, aren't you?
Come out.
I know you're there.
You need to learn how to talk to your brother.
To your senior.
Have you grown a bit more mature?
Still looking as pathetic as ever, huh?
It's been a while.
Zenitsu.
Kaigaku... you, who became a demon...
I no longer think of you as my brother.
Ah!
Water Breathing... Wind Slash...
Free Flow!
Do it!
Draw the blood!
Yes!
This world is insane.
The entire building is pulsing and writhing,
like it's alive.
It's trying to crush Giyuu-san and me.
We need to join up with the other Hashira as soon as possible
and head toward Muzan without getting separated.
Death!
Shinobu Kocho, death.
Due to combat with Upper Rank Two.
Death.
Yes.
What's the status of the other Hashira and the slain Demon Slayers?
They're in the center of the twelve-layered shield.
The Hashira are fighting demons, over ten of them.
Beyond that wall, more than thirty demons are approaching.
It continues.
What incredible power.
This is...
the infinite demon castle.
We were lured
into this infinite demon castle.
However,
we weren't just lured here.
Father made meticulous preparations
to face this day, to connect our fates.
He arranged the Hashira to rush to each other's aid,
and ensured the strongest Demon Slayers became Pillars,
entrusting Kasugai Crows with messages and waiting for the right moment.
With the help of Tamayo-san and Yushiro-san,
and to make it complete,
our parents and sisters gave their lives as well.
We won't lose this battle.
In this vast space, five immense forces radiate as if exerting their power.
Are these the Upper Ranks?
One of them is active at the same location where Shinobu was.
Upper Rank Six and Agatsuma are fighting together.
Upper Rank... Are there other Hashira?
No! It's just Agatsuma alone!
One Hinoe-rank slayer against an Upper Rank is tough.
Go help immediately!
You haven't changed, huh?
Short and pathetic.
Still such a weakling.
Have you gotten used to being a Hashira?
Hey, have you learned to use anything other than the First Form?
You got into the Upper Ranks by filling in the gaps,
and you seem pretty pleased about it.
Heh, you've learned to talk big, haven't you?
Why the hell did you become a demon?
Hahaha, to you,
someone with the talent for Thunder Breathing, why become a demon?
Because you became a demon, Jii-chan...
Jii-chan died by seppuku.
He cut his own stomach alone, without a second to assist.
When you commit seppuku, if no one cuts off your head, you suffer for a long time before dying!
He died using his own throat and heart!
He became a demon after mastering Thunder Breathing!
Who cares? So what? Should I feel sad?
Should I repent?
I don't bother with people who don't value me.
I always
no matter the time,
side with those who properly value me.
If that old man died suffering, good riddance.
I did so much for him,
but he didn't respect me.
He called a piece of trash like you a successor alongside me, that damn old man.
A former Hashira or not, I have no use for a senile old man.
Jii-chan wasn't senile. If I'm trash, you're scum.
Me, who could only master the First Form, and you, who could master every form except the First.
I feel so sorry for Jii-chan, who had no worthy successors.
You and I...
Don't you dare compare us!
Thunder Breathing...
Fourth Form!
Genius!
You're too slow, scum.
I got cut. This guy's fast.
His movements are like a different person.
I'm not wrong.
Kneeling to an overwhelmingly strong opponent isn't shameful.
As long as you survive, there's always a way.
You're not defeated until you die, even if you grovel or rub your head in the dirt.
Even if your house burns down, you drink muddy water, or your theft is exposed,
as long as you live, you can win someday. I'll show you victory.
That's what I've believed and followed.
Become a demon.
Do you desire even greater strength?
If you earn his approval,
you could join us.
The stronger the swordsman,
the longer it takes to become a demon.
It took me three days.
To turn someone who uses Breathing into a demon,
they need to receive a large amount of his blood.
And there are those whose bodies resist becoming demons,
but what about you?
What a generous offer.
But betraying that trust is absolutely forbidden.
If you betray it,
your head will roll alongside Douma's.
A tearful farewell.
That...
The terror that makes every cell in my body
scream and cry out.
Compared to that, this small fry is nothing.
Even with gained strength, you can't match an Upper Rank.
Agatsuma, this guy is trash.
Always crying and whining.
No skill, no guts.
Help me!
That damn old man called a weakling like you a successor alongside me.
Kaigaku,
Jii-chan...
He was a bit bigger than you,
but you and I being together?
No way in hell.
You deserve to die.
Both you and that old man deserve to die.
I could only master the First Form,
while you mastered every form except the First.
That's why Jii-chan
saw both of us
as joint successors of Thunder Breathing.
But you,
you wanted to deny that even by becoming a demon.
Thunder Breathing, Sixth Form.
Here we go!
Five consecutive strikes in a single breath.
You landed a big hit!
You can't even tell good from evil anymore!
I can tell good from evil.
What's wrong?
You're Muzan's favorite, aren't you?
Someone who received five vials from Muzan,
show me that power, you dragon!
What's wrong?
Are you out of steam?
Come on, hit me with it!
Thunder Breathing,
First Form.
Heh!
Thunderclap and Flash.
Hahaha!
Just charging straight in with that basic form?
You think that'll hit me?!
Thunder Breathing,
Third Form.
Thunder Swarm!
Like this, Aria!
I won't hold back!
How's that?
The sharpness of my blade, honed by my techniques,
cuts through skin and flesh,
resounding like a deadly poison!
Those who value and recognize me are good.
Those who undervalue and reject me are evil.
Got it? This is my power!
I became a demon!
Whether it's one strike or eight,
you, who can only do that, a successor?
What a ridiculous mistake!
Ya!
This is...
the answer you came up with...
I knew it...
I knew, but...
Zenitsu! This is... the end!
Thunder Breathing...
Sixth Form!
Rumble and Flash!
The explosive strikes will keep burning through your body!
Burn my power into your eyes and body!
I surpassed Thunder Breathing by becoming a demon!
I'm special!
I'm different from you!
Different from all of you!
As expected, Jii-chan made a mistake!
Kaigaku, you bastard!
A brother like you!?
The First Form of Thunder Breathing is the foundation of all forms, right?
If you can't use the First Form, then no matter what,
mastering the other forms doesn't mean much.
And yet, that guy Kaigaku acted so high and mighty.
He didn't become anything great.
He'll probably die soon.
Take that!
Even if you hit an Upper Rank,
don't cause trouble, you trash. Having someone like you around is such a pain.
I knew full well that Kaigaku hated me,
and I hated Kaigaku too.
But I respected him, from the bottom of my heart.
You worked hard and always looked forward.
I was always watching your back. You were special.
To Jii-chan, you were a special and precious person to me, but...
that wasn't enough, was it? No matter the time,
I could hear the sound of your discontent.
There’s a hole in the box that holds the happiness in your heart.
Happiness keeps spilling out.
If you don’t notice and patch that hole quickly, you’ll never be fulfilled.
Jii-chan.
I’m sorry.
Our paths...
have diverged.
Still got some strength left…
What?
I’m sorry,
big brother.
This place...
Ngh…
You didn’t escape…
What was that technique…?
Too fast…
A form I don’t know!
What did you use?
Damn it… damn it!
That old man really favored you, huh!
He taught you alone and not me!
No…
He created a seventh form.
That guy,
who could only use the First Form,
surpassed me.
Guh!
I can’t take it.
I can’t accept that fact.
To lose to a guy like that…
Am I losing?
It’s driving me insane.
No,
it’s not a loss! He’ll fall and die too.
That guy has no strength left.
He’ll die with me!
Those who don’t give to others will eventually receive nothing.
Someone who only takes ends up with nothing.
Because they can’t create anything themselves.
Dying alone is fitting, isn’t it?
Where am I?
Jii-chan!
I’m sorry.
I couldn’t get along with Kaigaku.
I even wrote him letters,
but he never replied.
If I hadn’t been there,
maybe Kaigaku wouldn’t have turned out like that.
Please forgive me.
I couldn’t repay you at all.
While Jii-chan was alive,
I wanted to become a Hashira,
to make you proud,
I’m sorry.
Jii-chan, I’m sorry.
You came to hate me.
Say something, Jii-chan.
What the—?
It’s tangled around my legs.
What are these?
Damn it!
Zenitsu.
You are my pride.
Shut up, Murata! Don’t act like you’re above me!
Stay sharp and watch your surroundings. If someone weaker than me gets taken out, I won’t forgive them!
I’m a demon, so why should I care about teamwork? I’m using the blood-stopper, but if the cracks on my face don’t heal, I’ll dodge even the urgent ones.
You hear me?
Don’t scare someone who’s already weak.
I’m using the blood-stopper too, but the bleeding won’t stop.
Stop it!
You’ll be fine! I’ll definitely save you!
You won’t die!
Hang in there, Agatsuma!
Keep fighting! Keep fighting!
The Upper Rank you fought hadn’t fully mastered their techniques or abilities yet.
You got lucky.
If this fight was a year later, you’d be dead instantly.
Don’t say depressing things!
I’m not saying anything wrong!
What’s that?
Yelling like that brought a demon!
Perfect timing.
Shinobu-san,
we’ll definitely win.
Everyone will,
we will.
What’s this shaking?
Giyuu-san!
Stop!
Calm down!
Is someone fighting again?
Is someone else going to die?
It’s been a while.
You did well to survive this long,
a weakling like you.
Um…
Tanjiro.
Yakada!
Aaaah!
Huh?
Ugh…
If Muzan dies, the other demons die too.
Then Kibutsuji Muzan is still alive.
Muzan’s power is probably being suppressed by Tamayo-san.
Even if it’s suppressed, it doesn’t react to Yushiro-san’s eyes.
Before Muzan’s power fully recovers,
we have to defeat him no matter what.
But in this infinite castle,
can we really find Kibutsuji Muzan?
No need to rush. You’re doing well.
He’ll definitely show himself. He came to me, didn’t he?
That’s the kind of man Kibutsuji Muzan is.
Understood, Father.
I’ll definitely finish this.
We need to find him before the Hashira’s strength runs out
and settle this.
Absolutely! Defeat Kibutsuji!
Please!
Got it.
I’m leaving this to you guys.
Go for it!
Now’s the time! Show the world what you’re made of!
Ora!
Mana… thank you.
Everyone’s fighting so hard.
Don’t cry.
Never stop moving forward.
We won’t lose.
Yes.
Lord Kirie,
you’re truly admirable.
Even amidst the pain of losing your father,
you take command of the Demon Slayer Corps
and carry out your mission with resolve.
Hey, Rengoku-san.
Exactly.
To inspire the children of the Corps
to stand so firmly like this.
I, too, as a mentor…
must keep running forward.
Protecting lives with my own.
You seem to be in pain.
The drug that Tamayo, the demon working with the Master, created…
I used it as instructed, but
will Nezuko really return to being human?
If Nezuko becomes human again, Muzan’s greatest desire will crumble.
The dream of a perfect being he’s pursued for over a thousand years,
overcoming the sun, will be reset to nothing.
Nezuko is the only one in all these years who doesn’t burn in sunlight.
Final Phase.
The words keep echoing in my mind.
On this journey,
my heart trembles.
My pulse races. This long battle might end tonight.
To think I’d be alive to witness it.
Feel it. Ever since you brought your demon sister,
it’s like a massive gear started turning.
If all the battles up to now were part of a giant machine,
you and Nezuko, two small gears, clicked into place,
and the stalled situation suddenly surged forward.
Don’t lose, Nezuko.
Don’t lose, Tanjiro.
Don’t lose, everyone!
Hinokami Kagura!
Here we go!
Go! Go! Go!
I can’t cut their arms!
I can’t cut their necks!
It’s gone.
I dodged the attack.
It’s working.
I can fight.
I couldn’t aim for the neck.
Hinokami Kagura! Sunflower Thrust!
Hah… Hah… Hah…
Hah… Hah…
Tanjiro… your techniques are finely honed.
Your skill is no exaggeration to say it rivals a Hashira.
To face an Upper Rank Three like this…
That day, in the snow, filled with despair,
weeping as you carried your sister,
you, who could only save your sister’s life…
Reveal your intent.
Technique Deployment.
Shall we begin?
Idle.
Ugh!